<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PREPARE</string>
    <string name="test_anxiety_questionaire">Test Anxiety Questionaire</string>
    <string name="sub_title">Sub title</string>
    <string name="prepare_a_companion_to_manage_exam_stress">Prepare: a companion to manage exam stress</string>
    <string name="find_out_support_nationwide">Find Out Support Nationwide</string>
    <string name="Intro_support_page">The services below offer a wide range of support if you need help for mental health issues.</string>
    <string name="Call">Call 116 123 to talk to <a href="https://www.samaritans.org/how-we-can-help/contact-samaritan/">
        Samaritans,</a> or email: jo@samaritans.org for a reply within 24 hours</string>
    <string name="Intro_sam">If you just need to talk, any time of day or night</string>
    <string name="TextShout">Text "SHOUT" to 85258 to contact the Shout Crisis Text Line, or text "YM" if you\'re under 19</string>
    <string name="title_activity_breathe">BreatheActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>


    <string name="box_breathing_info">Box breathing is a technique used in taking slow deep breaths\n
        \nThis can heighten performance and concentration whiles being a stress reliever.
    </string>
    <string name="intro_nhs">If you need help urgently for your mental health,
        but it\'s not an emergency</string>
    <string name="speak_gp">Call 111 OR\n\nSpeak to your GP to advise you about helpful treatments and
        also help you access mental health services.
      </string>
    <string name="student_mind_intro">Student Mind</string>
    <string name="student_mind">Student Mind the UK\'s student mental health charity.</string>
    <string name="student_mind1">You can access the services and support content they offer<a href="https://www.studentminds.org.uk/"> here</a>
    </string>
    <string name="student_nightline_intro">Student Nightline</string>
    <string name="nightline">You can speak to someone from your university about anything <a href="https://www.nightline.ac.uk/want-to-talk/"> here</a></string>
    <string name="nightline_intro">Nightline is a listening, emotional support, information and supplies service, run by students for students.</string>
    <string name="FirstRoutine"><ul><li><b>First</b></li></ul>: Create a weekly schedule.
        Write out a weekly schedule based on class time activities, free time and job activities
    </string>
    <string name="Estimate"><ul><li><b>Second</b></li></ul>: Estimate the average amount needed for each subject to obtain a specific grade</string>
    <string name="Freetime"><ul><li><b>Third</b></li></ul>: Schedule blocks of free time between subjects and assign them to study a particular subject
    </string>
    <string name="Write"><ul><li><b>Fourth</b></li></ul>: Write down what you do whilst studying.Examples are breaks, nervousness.Note the length of time it takes to get started on the assignment</string>
    <string name="SummaryRoutine1">Monitoring of behaviour can lead to change</string>
    <string name="intro_skill2">A research showed that University students obtaining higher grades reported the following about themselves:</string>
    <string name="skill2Routine1"><ul><li>Although Students did not assign themselves a specific time to study each subject, they set aside a specific time to study everyday</li></ul></string>
    <string name="skill2Routine2"><ul><li>They usually studied during the day between classes and made enjoyable activities upon completing a definite assignment</li></ul></string>
    <string name="skill2Routine3"><ul><li>They studied alone</li></ul></string>
    <string name="skill2Routine4"><ul><li>They studied a subject continuously for an hour rather than skipping between subjects</li></ul></string>
    <string name="skill2Routine5"><ul><li>They began working on voluminous assignments long before the due date</li></ul></string>
    <string name="skill2Routine6"><ul><li>They obtained 3–6 hours of exercise each week</li></ul></string>
    <string name="skill2Routine7"><ul><li>They spent less time studying material specific to a subject than students receiving lower grades</li></ul></string>
    <string name="SQ_intro">SQ3R method is one of the effective ways of transferring reading materials into memory.\n<p>The process involves five steps : scan,question,read,recite and review.</p></string>
    <string name="SQ_scan"><b>Scan</b>\n<p>\nLook over an entire chapter, attempt to gain a general understanding of what the author is saying.\n Look at major headings and relationships between them.
        Read the summary as it provides an overview of what the author thinks its important. \n\nYou can take 5 minutes to complete this activity, picking 5-7 points which are important in the chapter
    </p></string>
    <string name="SQ_question"><b>Question</b>\n<p>\nWhat are you about to read? Transform major and minor headings into questions and write them into a notebook.
        This allows you to review chapters using a problem solving frame of reference. Areas of strengths and weakness could be be identified
        through this process when revising for an exam.</p> \n<p>The three types of questions which are important</p>
        \n<ul><li>Definitions</li></ul>\n
        \n<ul><li>Similarities and Differences</li></ul>\n
        \n<ul><li>Examples</li></ul>
    </string>
    <string name="SQ_read"><b>Read</b> \n<p>\nRead the chapter carefully now to find answers to questions you have written down.
        You can highlight the answers by the following options:</p>\n
        \n<p><ul><li>Using a personal notation system in the margin of the chapters to quickly find information when revising.
        Example I=Important, S=Summary VI=Very Important
        \n\n<ul><li>Writing the answers in a notebook under the questions.Use key phrases that will trigger recitation of concepts to avoid lengthy answers in notebook.</li></ul>\n
        \nFocus on these major points when reading a specific chapter:
        \n<ul><li>The fist sentence of the paragraph. The rest of the lines usually explains the main point in the first line</li></ul>\n
        \n<ul><li>Take note of graphs,table and charts, they summarize key concepts</li></ul>\n
        \n<ul><li>Key Phrases which explain important information follow words like "firstly,secondly, thirdly and summary".</li></ul>
        </li></ul></p></string>
    <string name="SQ_recite"><b>Recite</b>\n<p>\nRecite answers to questions after reading a whole chapter.
        This produces a rapid method of learning from both verbal and auditory channel.</p>
    </string>
    <string name="SQ_review"><b>Review</b>\n<p>\nReview material after answering all questions in the chapter.
        You should take less than 5 minutes to reanswer questions in the chapter from memory. A material that cannot be verbalised is not know.
    </p></string>
    <string name="skill4routine1"><ul><li>One hour lectures usually contains 3–6 main points</li></ul></string>
    <string name="introSkill4">This section is about lecture notes and preparing for exams, the following can be followed:</string>
    <string name="skill4_routine2">Lecturers may present materials in this manner:\n

        <ul><li>Present overview of material that will be covered</li></ul>\n
        <ul><li>State the main points and label them as important
    </li></ul></string>
    <string name="skill4_routine3">Personal interest of examiner may appear in exams, be aware of them and the examiner\'s philosophy of testing\n
        \n<ul><li>Terms such as "being able to apply what you have learnt" implies problem and analogy type questions in exams</li></ul>\n
        \n<ul><li>"Knowing the basics" implies short answer and similarities and differences questions.</li></ul> \n
        \n<ul><li>The lecture itself will provide materials for an exam through handouts.</li></ul></string>

    <string name="skill4_routine4">Always organise lecture notes after you write them down.
    Do the following after lectures: \n
        <ul><li>Take a few minutes to skim over notes</li></ul>\n
        \n<ul><li>Write down sentences to summarize main points</li></ul>\n
    \n<ul><li>Write down points you need clarification for the next lecture</li></ul>
    </string>
    <string name="skill4_routine5"><i>Procedures that can help manage anxiety while preparing to take an exam:</i>\n
        <ul><li>Arrive early at the test centre</li></ul>\n
        \n<ul><li>Bring the proper materials</li></ul>\n
        \n<ul><li>Avoid discussions with others about possible questions and answers</li></ul>\n
        \n<ul><li>If you cannot recall some material during the exam, try not to panic.</li></ul>
    </string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Click on the button below to begin creating your reminder!</string>
    <string name="how_is_the_assessment_calculated"><b>How is the assessment calculated?</b></string>
    <string name="answer_to_question">You will be asked to rate how often you have been affected by a
    number of factor from \'not at all\' to  \'always\'.\n \nThere are 10 questions and your total score shows your current level of test anxiety.
    </string>
    <string name="assement_duration">The assessment will take no more than five minutes.
        <p>You will also get a feedback based on what you score from the assessment</p></string>
    <string name="average_anxiety">2.0 - 2.5 - Normal or average test anxiety \nYour score suggest a normal test anxiety level.
                    "\nThis is only an indicator of how you are feeling at the moment"
                    " \n\nCome back and re take this assessment if things change</string>
    <string name="high_normal_anxiety">2.5 - 2.9 - High normal test anxiety \nYour score suggests a mild test anxiety"
                    " \n\nYour might find the tools in this app helpful in maintaining your well being</string>
    <string name="moderately_high_anxiety">3.0 - 3.4 - Moderately high (some items rated 4=high) \nYour score suggest a moderately high test anxiety"
                    " The symptoms may be interfering with your life and maybe causing some distress but may feel manageable"
                    "\nThe tools in this app can help with some of the symptoms you are experiencing</string>
    <string name="high_anxiety">3.5 - 3.9 - High test anxiety \nYour score suggest you have a high test anxiety, "
                    "You may want to speak with your GP/Doctor or use a counselling service"
                    "\n\nIf your symptoms are causing distress."
                    "\n\nThe tools in the app  provide some helpful tools to manage symptoms alongside treatment if you require it</string>
    <string name="extremely_high_anxiety">4.0-5.0 -Extremely high anxiety , \nYour score suggests that you are experiencing high levels of test anxiety at the moment" +
                    " We recommend booking an appointment with your GP or University Counselling services right away"
                    "as there are many tools that could help you through this"
                    "\n\n If you need to speak to someone urgently, you can speak to A&amp;E department or"
                    "talk to the Samaritans available 24/7(find them on the support page of the app</string>
    <string name="low_anxiety">1.0 - 1.9 - Comfortably low test anxiety
Your score suggests that you are not experiencing test anxiety at the moment</string>


</resources>